小愿8压制组 原创翻译
翻译｜寓　小愿8　tifhadu
校对｜隔壁家的孩子　　时间轴｜小愿8
字幕转制｜天外生物
感谢原字幕制作者
五年前
你就不能开快点吗
Speed it up, will you?
你开车跟老太婆一样
You drive like my granny.
在一堆车子中 我有什么办法
We're moving with the flow of traffic.
什么时候轮我开
When do I get to drive?
我的车 所以 不
My car, so, never.
我在创建一个推特账户
Ooh, I'm gonna sign in this thing called Twitter.
就像你可以吧我喜欢吃披萨发出去
You put up what you're thinking like, I love pizza,
或者 我正在吃披萨 甚至是 披萨太棒了
or I'm having pizza now, or even pizza is awesome.
你们每天脑子里不会只有披萨吧
All your thoughts don't have to be pizza related.
谁说的
Says who?
嘿 我们可以在这时
Hey, I could order a pizza,
定一个披萨
while we're puttering along here.
噢 好主意
Ooh, great idea.
马上就能吃上披萨咯
Gonna have pizza soon.
已推送
First twit sent.
那是什么玩意
What the heck is that?
- 闪电侠 去看下  - 收到
- Flash, go find out.  - On it.
- 报告  - 你需要自己来看
- Report.  - You need to see for yourself.
我没法完全确定
I'm not totally sure.
终于有事做了 我们先阻止那恐怖五人组
Big week for us. First, we stop the fearsome five.
他们一定会这么说
They were so pissed.
你们要为此付出付出代价
You'll pay for interfering with us.
什么什么的
Blah, blah, blah.
先做正事
And now we get to stop an alien brawl.
我们该站哪一边
Which side do we join?
- 不是吧  - 不能以貌取人
- Really?  - Looks can be deceiving.
少年泰坦 出击
Titans, go!
这个决定可与她很性感没一点关系
And the fact that she's hot has nothing to do with it.
闪开 蜥蜴唇
Buzz off, lizard lips!
借过 抱歉
Coming through. Excuse me.
抱歉[法语]
Excusez-moi
我想长发公主想告诉我们些什么
I think Rapunzel is trying to tell us something.
快手 你有足够大的家伙能把那玩意关上吗
Speedy, you got something loud to close that thing?
没问题 老大
Got you covered, boss.
这我可没料到
I did not see that coming.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我是来自塔马兰的柯莉安妲
I am Koriand'r of Tamaran.
我们一族人可以通过亲吻习得对方的语言
Our kind can learn language from the act of kissing.
不错
Useful.
你还好吗
Are you all right?
我的姐妹 柯曼得 篡权了王位
My sister, Komand'r, staged a coup and took the throne.
我不得不逃走
I had to flee.
但我很快就会回去
But I will soon return.
好吧 你可以跟我们呆在一起 直到你想出解决办法来
Well, you can stay with us until you figure it out.
好吗
Okay?
好的 请麻烦你
Yes, please.
我寻求两到三天的庇护
I will ask sanctuary for two or three days.
最长一周
A week at the longest.
让我来为你介绍我的朋友们
Let me introduce you to my friends.
哦对了 我能说点西班牙语
Oh, by the way, I speak some Spanish,
倘若你想学的话…
if you wanna learn that.
还有法语
Second year high school French.
欢迎来到少年泰坦
Welcome to the Teen Titans.
少年泰坦
少年泰坦：犹大契约
现在
小心点你个蠢货
Careful, you fool.
这设备比你的命都值钱
This equipment is worth more than your lives.
什么
What?
少年泰坦在不到一分钟的时间里就会找过来
The Titans will be there in less than a minute.
我怎么没看出来
I see no signs of that.
信 或者不信 你的选择
Believe, don't believe, your choice.
他们有防备
They're ready.
可惜太慢了
They're slow.
我还没有回贴
I hardly had time to answer a post.
爬上去太明显了 而且还有月光
It's a tough climb, especially in this moonlight.
夜翼
Nightwing.
它们会发现我们的
They're bound to spot us.
夜翼
Nightwing.
如果我们等那些云
If we wait for those clouds...
迪克
Dick!
干嘛
What?
土石女会把我们带上去的
Terra is taking us up there.
是吗
She is?
是 这儿所有脏活都是我的
Yeah, I do all the dirty work around here.
往上
Going up.
你离开太久了 牛仔
You've been gone a long time, cowboy.
行动
Let's move.
安静
Quiet down.
圣甲虫在害怕
The bug is nervous.
我也没多少信心
I'm not feeling too good about this myself.
你怎么能这么冷静
How come you're so calm?
因为你从没当过地鼠
You have never been a gopher.
圣甲虫 停下来
Scarab, stop.
你最好控制住那东西 甲壳虫
Control that thing, Beetle,
要么我就替你动手了
or I'll control it for you.
你打算在这地方舞刀弄枪
You're going to have a sword fight in here?
要不给你换个更像样点的地方  比如扫帚间
How about some place roomier like a broom closet?
所有人 冷静下来
Everyone, calm down.
敌人就在我们上面
The enemy is above us.
任务是一切
You have to channel all your thoughts to that.
记住 这些不是一般的敌人
Remember, these opponents are different.
呃 就像柯莉告诉你们的那样
Uh, as Kori will tell you.
不不 没关系请继续讲
No, keep going.
自从我离开泰坦 我一直在研究这些敌人
I've been studying them since I left the Titans.
他们是极端狂热份子
They're zealots, extremists.
为了打倒你 他们可以不眨眼睛就牺牲掉自己
They'll sacrifice themselves without hesitation to get to you.
所以 我们得尽快打败他们 越快越好
So, the quicker we take them down, the better.
这样差不多了
That about cover it?
讲的非常好
Very well said.
土石女 你还能坚持住吗
Terra, can you do this?
当然 倘若你们都闭嘴的话
Yes, if you'd all shut up.
现在距离地板只有六英尺
We're six inches under the floor.
谁想敲敲门
Who wants to knock?
泰坦 出击
Titans, go!
谢谢带我们潜入了这个压根没法潜入的蜂巢基地 土石女
Thanks for getting us into the impenetrable H.I.V.E base, Terra.
是啊 你是最棒的
Yeah, you're the best.
这个坏蛋是你的 老妈
This bad guy is yours, mama.
土石女 跟紧我们
Terra, stay with us.
说得好像我一没你们就不行了
Like I couldn't take out all these jokers by myself.
我们这里已经暴露了
We've been compromised.
遗弃基地
Abandon the base.
他们准备得还不错
They prepared well.
反应也迅速
Their reaction time is much better.
罗宾 别再恭维这些坏蛋了
Robin, stop complementing the bad guys.
至少有一点他说对了 时刻准备着
But he's right. Be ready for anything.
这些家伙的装备肯定是批发的
These dudes must buy their bad guy stuff in bulk.
要不我们试试你上周末教我的那个怎么样
How about we do that move you taught me last weekend?
在这地方
Now?
我无所谓 但他们就不知道了
I admire your boldness, but what will the team think?
等等 不是这意思
What? No, not...
好吧 我怕了你
Okay, you got me.
是说我们训练的那一招 请
The training move, please.
上卡车
Get in the truck.
你们的义务已尽
Your service has come to an end.
再见
Bless you all.
小心点 哥们儿 那些可是我的朋友
Watch it, dude. Those are my friends.
别搞得在像在管束你舍友一样 甲壳
At least act like you're trying to keep your parasite in line, Beetle.
胆子真小
That was unbearable.
你说呢
Get it?
无聊
Seriously?
你能别把自己暴露给敌人吗
Could you not leave yourself open like that?
我担心
I worry.
对不起宝贝
I'm sorry, babe.
我最近想了很多
I've been doing a lot of thinking lately.
关于什么的
About what?
我觉得我们的关系应该进展到下一步
I think we should take the next step in our relationship.
下次再说
To be continued.
说茄子
Say cheese,
发送
and post.
晚上一起看电影怎么样
Hey, how about a movie tonight?
继续走你的 马盖拉
Keep moving, Magilla.
基地是我们的了
The base is ours.
刚才我们被打断前 你打算说什么来着
So, what were you saying before we were interrupted?
我
I...
好吧 哪都一样
Okay, good a place as any.
我在城里有一所公寓
I got an apartment in the city.
也许我们能分享一下
I hoped, maybe, we could share, you know,
你知道 住一起
together.
哦 好吧
Oh, snap!
里面竟然不是一颗石头
No rock?
这可真够差劲的
That's so lame.
在塔玛拉 我们其实很随便的
On Tamaran, everyone would gossip.
所以我们可以住在一起
So it's a good thing we live here.
我觉得他们不太传统
What I'm getting is that they're too good to hang with us.
是吗 你在嫉妒吗
Yeah, that's the takeaway.
粉丝过百万了
Hey, I'm over a million followers!
我赢了
Call me Jefe.
你得把注意力放在游戏上
You need to get your head in the game, gar.
或者你的心思在另一种游戏上
Or, maybe your head is in a different game.
我这么棒 竟然没人约我
Who wouldn't want to date me? I'm awesome.
可我不管做什么 都没用
But everything I do pisses her off.
想听听我的建议
Want my advice?
别再变成猩猩然后去偷吻了
Quit turning into a chimp and stealing monkey kisses.
可人们觉得那样可爱啊
People think that's adorable.
不 没人那么想
Nope, no one thinks that.
好了
Time out.
我得去打通电话
Gotta make a call.
土石女
Terra.
陪我过几招
Would you like to join me?
这东西能帮我沉下心来
The staff helps clear the mind.
不 谢谢
No thanks.
我只想离那绿豆子远一点
I'm just trying to avoid green bean for a while.
我从来都不关心动物园发生了什么
I never cared much for the zoo.
如果他骚扰你…
If he's bothering you...
他只是个混蛋
He's just a jerk.
关于她的流言是真的吗
Is it true what they say about her,
她父亲被她困在了她额间的宝石里
that she has her father trapped in that Jewel on her head?
是的 他的名字叫鬼父
Yes, his name is Trigon.
他是一个恶魔
He's a demon.
他们之间有间隙
They have issues.
好吧 起码她知道去哪能找到她的父亲
Well, she knows where she can find him.
你该多和她谈谈
You should talk to her more.
你就会发现渡鸦非常
You'll find that Raven can be quite
有趣
interesting.
不 谢谢了 我有点怕她
No thanks. Too creepy for me.
米拉格罗 听起来不错
Sounds like a good time, Milagro.
你拿到我的礼物了吗
Did you get my gift?
当然 永远的十七岁的礼品卡 我的最爱
Sure did. Gift card to the seventeen forever. My favorite.
妈妈和爹地想跟你说话 爱你
Mom and dad wanna say hi. Love you.
瞧我的宝贝儿子
There's my baby boy!
你能吃饱饭吗
Are you getting enough to eat?
是啊 你过得怎么样
Yeah, how's it goin'?
还是不太喜欢我 哼
Still doesn't like me, huh?
他在改变
It's getting better.
别提那东西了
Let's not talk about that thing.
转眼两年过去了
It's been two years.
我正在努力 爸爸
I'm working on it, dad.
但这很难 你知道
But it's hard, you know.
他有自己的想法
It's got a mind of its own.
- 还有自己的脾气  - 奥多
- And a temper.  - Aldo.
他和一群超级英雄在一起
For god's sake. He's with a bunch of super heroes.
超人或是谁能把那东西弄下来
You think superman or someone could take that thing off him.
你应该冷静一点
You're supposed to calm down.
我们不能把每次通电话都这样结束
We can't have every call end this way, Aldo.
海梅不想我们讨论这个问题
Jaime won't wanna talk to us.
为什么是蛋糕
Why is the cake
出去吗 这不是时候
coming out? It's not time!
啊 你的姨妈 慷苏拉 简直神经了
Ah, your aunt, Consuela, esta loca.
去吧 妈妈 我们可以之后再聊
Go, mom, we can talk later.
我爱你 海梅
I love you, Jaime.
保重
Be good.
慷苏拉 把蛋糕给我
Consuela, give me that cake!
我最好也走了
I better go too.
真抱歉 只是
I'm sorry. It's just...
我想我的儿子
I miss my son.
正在打开最近的 血兄弟 片段
Accessing most recent footage on brother blood.
一派胡言
Lies.
我的教堂是神圣的地方
My church is a holy place
我们唯一的使命是做正确的事
and we strive only to do good.
拜托  血兄弟
Come now, brother blood.
你的教堂难道不是另一个光荣化的邪教吗
Isn't your church just a glorified cult?
不像你 布赖斯 我坚信着美国
Unlike you, Bryce, I believe in an America
所有信仰都应被给予应有的尊重
where all beliefs should be treated with respect.
可耻的事媒体认为并非如此
It's a shame the press doesn't.
恐怕这是我们能从血会得到的所有消息了
I'm afraid that's all we're going to get from brother blood.
我是彼得森 布赖斯
I'm Bryce Peterson.
晚安
-Have a good night.
祖父一定会为血兄弟
Grandfather would have been impressed with blood,
经营着像蜂巢一样一个世界范围的邪教而骄傲
running a worldwide cult as well as H.I.V.E.
他们本为一体
They're the same thing.
只是让他们看起来是分开的而已
He just makes them look separate.
你从来都不脱掉那制服吗
Do you ever get out of that uniform?
只有洗澡时候才脱
Only when I bathe.
也许是时候了
Might be time.
没味道
I'm good.
我出去了
Goin' out.
我听说你总是出去
I hear you're gone a lot.
你去哪
Where do you go?
你知道我是不需要大人管小孩
You realize I'm not a child who needs permission to go outside.
对吧
Correct?
达米安 我不是在审问
Damien, I wasn't interrogating.
只是感兴趣而已
Just taking an interest.
我出去巡逻
I go out on patrol.
对了  恭喜你有了新欢 格雷森
By the way, I should offer congratulations on your cohabitation, Grayson.
星火证明她是一个够格的领袖
Starfire has proven herself to be a decent leader.
我同意
I approve.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你在蜂巢文件里找到什么了吗
Have you found anything in the H.I.V.E. Files?
没什么  但我仍在查
Nothing Earth-shaking, but I'm still checking.
听起来你什么都没查到
Sounds like you got squat.
我至少还能享受下正常生活
I love endangering my life for nothing.
上次突袭拿到的新的文件
Which is why I've added the newest files to the ones
已经损毁的无法阅读了
too damaged to read, from the previous raids.
希望电脑能为我们找到其中的关联
I'm hoping the computer will find a connection we missed.
程序得花一到两天处理这些信息
It may take the program a day or two.
至少还有希望
Not your worst idea.
干嘛
What?
呃
Ugh!
嘿 你们谁见杰米了
Hey, anyone seen Jaime?
他就在那儿
Yeah, he's right there.
有点不对劲
Something is wrong.
是啊 他输掉球赛了
Yeah, there is. He's about to be crushed at Foosball.
你想来瞧瞧嘛
You wanna come see?
起开
Buzz off.
也许你应该去
Maybe you should go.
也许你们两个都去是个好主意
Might be good to have two of you down there.
如我所说 不服从的人
And I say to you. Those who deny the chosen,
在即将建立的乐园中没有栖脚的地方
have no place in the Eden that shall be built.
罪人和亵渎者 那些与我们价值观念不同的人
Sinners and blasphemers who do not share our values
将被抛弃
need not apply,
兄弟姊妹们
brothers and sisters.
全能的 兄弟血会
Hail, brother blood!
万岁 万岁 万岁
Hail, hail, hail.
全能的 血色兄弟
Hail, brother blood.
万岁 万岁 万岁
Hail, hail, hail...
啊 你在这儿 迈赫姆
Ah, there you are, mayhem.
你为何
Punctual as always.
这么冷静的
How can you be so calm?
这是第三个被少年泰坦摧毁的基地
That was the third base the Titans have destroyed.
我的计划历经九百年的风雨
My plan is nine centuries in the making.
每个年代都有人反抗
In every age, there are always those who oppose me.
但如你所见
But as you can see,
我总是赢家
I am always victorious.
这是那个记者吗
Is that the reporter?
是他
Yes.
我们的朋友再也不会问出那些粗鲁的问题了
Our friend won't be asking impertinent questions anymore.
他的质疑远不及少年泰坦带来的威胁
His heresy does not compare to the titan's threat.
我们几乎无法逃脱他们
We barely escaped them.
但你做到了
But you did,
因为他警告过你
because he warned you.
我们的守护天使
Our guardian angel.
别做无谓的担心了
Oh, stop your fretting, mayhem.
他会保证泰坦不捣乱
He'll keep the Titans at bay.
我已预见
I've foreseen it.
再加上 我付那混蛋足够的钱
Plus, I pay the bastard enough.
你能慢点吗 杰米
Could you slow down, Jaime?
那你回塔上吧
Go back to the tower then.
没人请你来
Nobody asked you to come.
噢 别这样 我们可是挺你的
Oh, come on. We're here to support you.
我可不是
I'm not.
我的意思是 我尊重杰米的意见
What I mean is, I respect Jaime not wanting to talk.
事实上 有些人应该好好学学怎么闭上他的嘴巴
In fact, more people should learn to shut their mouths.
好吧 那可真没意思
Well, that's no fun.
呃 好吧 我闭嘴
Uh, okay, I give up.
瞧
The center.
我的父母在乡下也做义工
My parents volunteer for the one in my town.
所以…
And...
也许我也该做义工
Maybe I should volunteer.
是的 没错儿
Yeah, right.
我们是泰坦
We're Titans.
我们不是给人舀汤的
We don't serve soup.
你不需要非得移动座山
You don't have to move a mountain
才算帮助别人 泰拉
to help people, Terra.
况且 我得想个办法
Besides, I gotta find a way to make the bug
让虫子在人类附近觉得更加舒服
more comfortable around humans.
我能帮你什么吗
Can I help you?
是的 呃
Yes, um,
崔西
Traci.
我想知道如果我想做义务劳动应该找谁
I was wondering who I can speak to about volunteering?
找我就对了
That would be me.
这下好了
And there it is.
仅仅因为我们的超能力
Just because we have powers
并不意味着我们就不能 你知道
doesn't mean we can't, you know,
建立关系
have relationships.
你不觉得吗
Don't you think?
嘿 享受生活没错儿 对吗
Hey, there's nothing wrong with having a life, right?
杀了她
Kill her!
杀了这个恶魔
Kill the demon!
怎么了
What's the matter?
没什么
Nothing.
真是差劲 我要离开
This is lame. I'm out.
在这千年里  我在敌人的血中沐浴
For nearly a millennium, I have bathed in my enemy's blood,
这么做
and for some mysterious reason,
可以使我永生
it has provided me immortality.
我总是好奇为什么
I have often wondered why?
为什么是我
Why me?
但现在我知道了
But now I know.
这是 天意让我
It was meant to bring me to this age,
在此地 在此时
this place, this moment,
借助科技的力量
where technology can at last be made to serve my greatness.
运行
Proceed.
你做的非常好
You've done well.
开始准备 迈赫姆 时机已到
Advance the preparations, mayhem. The time has come
让我们永生之荣耀
for us to move from immortality to glory.
多谢你的付出
Your service has come to an end.
祝福你 我的孩子
Bless you, my son.
作为宇宙公主
For a space Princess,
你的东西还真不少
you sure have a lot of stuff.
我还是小女孩的时候就有这个了
I've had this since I was a little girl.
这是我唯一有时间拿走的东西
It was the only thing I had time to take.
又来
Not again.
泰拉 你还好吗
Terra, are you okay?
她就快要把整个楼都弄到了
She's going to bring the building down.
我能帮助她
I can help.
你在干吗
What are you doing?
滚开
Get off me!
你在发动你的能力  土石女
You were shaking everything, Terra.
我们来看你
We came to check on you.
你还好吗
Are you all right?
只是个该死的噩梦罢了
It's a freaking nightmare.
你们快走吧 让我一个人静一静
Just leave me alone.
我很好 所以 走吧
I'm okay, so, get going.
你们听见我说的乐 走啊
You heard me. Get going.
还有你 绿豆芽
You too, greeny.
这种事发生得多吗
Does that happen a lot?
足够多
It happens enough.
- 你看到什么了  - 什么都没看到
- What did you see?  - Nothing.
而且就算我看到任何东西也跟你没关系
And if I did see anything, it wouldn't be your business.
塔里发生的一切都跟我有关系
Everything that goes on in the tower is my business.
不管是谁
Just like it should be for all of you.
据我所知 达米安 柯莉安才是头 而不是你
The last I checked, Damien, Kori was in charge, not you.
很高兴再次见到你 我的朋友
So good to see you again, my friends.
已经过去太长的时间
It's been too long.
太长了
Too long.
别把这搞得神经兮兮 布拉德
Don't make this weirder than it already is, blood.
你是说装束
Are you referring to the setting?
我自己从中获取力量
I myself take strength from it.
墓地不是一个该被畏惧的地方
The cemetery isn't a place to be feared.
而是重生的地方
It's a place of renewal.
对你我见面的地方我没有任何意见
I have no problem meeting anywhere you want,
但我担心我的雇主是个神经病
but I get concerned when my employer talks to himself.
我在跟死者说话
I talk to the dead,
无论尸体如何腐烂 总是有一线生气存留
for no matter how rotted the corpse, there's always a tiny wisp of life left.
有时候足够把它们带回来
Sometimes enough life to bring them back.
你们都该明白
You of all people should know that.
你想要什么 布拉德
What do you want, blood?
我想在一周内得到进展
I want to move everything up by a week.
我已经等待了足够久的时间 丧钟
I've waited long enough, Deathstroke.
这不是我们约好的
That wasn't the deal.
我会付你双倍的酬金
I'll double your price.
这可以接受吗
Is that acceptable?
就像之前 我要所有的泰坦
As before, I want all the Titans.
你能做到吗
Can you do it?
时刻准备着
To be ready for anything,
你们必须为一切情况而训练
you must train for everything.
这是欧喀拉的军阀教我的
That was the most important lesson
最 刻骨铭心的教训
instilled in me by the warlords of Okaara.
又是他们
Dude... Them again?
老兄
Dude...
这同样应该在你们的心中铭记
And so it shall be instilled in you.
让我们对练
Let's pair off.
那些不在战斗中的 就观察学习
Those not fighting, watch and learn.
夜翼
Nightwing.
让我们起舞 先生
Shall we dance, good sir?
当然 我的女士
But of course, my lady.
看来我们知道是孰强孰弱了
Guess we know who's taking out the garbage at the new place.
这对你没一点好处
That was not a confidence booster.
你做的非常好
You did very well.
你这次坚持的时间远远要比以前久
You lasted far longer this time.
我当然指的是训练
I meant in training, of course.
当我们… 他可是非常熟练
He's very proficient when we have...
柯莉
Kori!
蓝甲虫 渡鸦
Blue Beetle, Raven.
抱歉 渡鸦 虫子不想输
Sorry, Raven, the bug doesn't wanna lose.
难道你想
And you do?
真对不起 你还好吗
Dios mio! I'm so sorry. Are you okay?
你在做什么
What the hell are you doing?
阿 我没事
Ah, I'm fine.
父亲觉得我让自己蒙羞
But dad feels I've disgraced myself.
所以就很好
So that's nice.
野兽小子 土石女 你们准备好了吗
Beast Boy, Terra, you ready?
抱歉
Right. Sorry.
我会让着土石女的
I'll take it easy on Terra.
我可很享受让你闭嘴
I'm gonna enjoy shutting you up.
除非你能抓到我 老妈
Only if you catch me, mama.
亲爱的 就让我给你一个大拥抱
Mon Cherie, let Garfield give you a big hug.
嗯 好软
Mmm, so soft.
亲下你再放你走
I let you go for a little kiss.
杀了她
Kill her!
女巫 你罪有应得
Now, witch, you get what's coming to you!
你管谁叫女巫
Who you calling a witch?
土石女
Terra!
她打算杀了他
She's going to kill him!
啊
Argh!
土石女 控制你自己
Terra, control yourself!
什么
What?
怎么回事
What's going on?
抱歉 这不是我的错
I'm sorry, it's not my fault.
- 让我平静下你的心  - 不
- Let me calm your mind.  - No!
- 别碰我  - 没关系的 土石女 我们理解
- Don't touch me.  - It's okay Terra, we understand.
放松
Take a breath.
我们在这里是为了你
We're here for you.
是啊 我知道你并不想伤害我 只是我做的太过了
Yeah. I know you didn't mean to hurt me. I took it too far.
你们这些人是怎么回事儿
What's wrong with you people?
我知道你打算说什么 土石女需要更多的训练
I know what you're going to say. Terra needs more training.
不 是别的事儿
No, it's something else.
她知道一些
She knows.
自从我们谈过之后 我已经感受到了关于土石女的一些东西
Since we talked, I have sensed something off about Terra.
格雷森 我们要多注意她
She needs to be watched, Grayson.
她需要理解而不是监视
She needs understanding not surveillance.
土石女 她虽然不是完人  但科里认为她是值得的
Terra, has her rough edges. But Corey thinks she's worth it.
我同意他的
And I agree.
你的仁慈 迟早会出事
Making decisions with your heart will get people killed.
不能有人和我
It's not like I can't sense the vibrations of someone following me.
即使他们在屋顶上
Even if they are on a roof.
我知道你不喜欢这个
I know what it's like not to fit in with the group.
什么错
What's wrong?
猴子男孩 渡鸦
Aside from monkey boy making me melt down, or Raven staring all the time,
还有夜翼 像个老妈妈 海梅还有他的甲虫
Nightwing, acting like a den mother, Jaime and his freako bug,
嗯 还有你 我的又一个暗恋者
miss smiles-a-lot, and you, my new stalker,
你没什么要说吧
huh, nothing I guess.
你需要我们的帮助
If you need to talk
就告诉我们
let us help you.
多么贴心的男孩
Such an observant, considerate boy.
你不会是真心的吧
You would think he truly cares.
斯莱德 你还没死啊
Slade? Look what hell just spit up.
退后
Stay back.
让我猜猜 他们不要你吗
Let me guess, they got you to a Lazarus pit, just in time.
先让你过过嘴瘾
Yes, I've been bathing in it quite a bit, lately.
待会就
You might say, it's addictive.
要你哭
Improves muscle tone too.
你的锋芒没了
Losing your edge.
你的朋友让你变的软弱
Your friends have made you soft.
就像我说的
Like I said, soft.
怎么这么久
Took you long enough.
你背叛了我们 为什么
You betrayed us, why?
背叛
Betrayed?
我从来就不是你们这边的
That assumes I was ever on your side in the first place.
给你 费尔南德斯先生
There you go, Mr. Fernandez.
- 很高兴有你的帮忙  谢谢你  - 不
- Great to have your help. Thanks.  - No.
应该是我说谢谢
Thank you.
这里
I kinda needed this.
让我想起了家
This just reminds me of home.
- 高温  - 小心
- Ow! Huh, hot.  - Careful.
你可不想被烧伤吧
You don't wanna get burned.
你有听到什么吗
Do you hear that?
- 好像在那  - 嗯…
- I heard it before.  - Uh...
我希望他们命够长
I hope there's not a short.
我想我知道它们在哪里
I think I heard it move over there.
我知道我心跳的很厉害
I know my pulse is racing.
但我没有危险 没有
But I'm in no danger. None.
不需要防御措施 我 怎么解释
Defensive measures are not needed. Oh, boy, how do I explain this?
称为性吸引力
There's something humans call sexual attraction.
唉 命啊
Aye, my life.
嗯 海梅
Uh, Jaime?
你在做什么
What are you doing?
我以为这会让你更舒服
I thought I'd get more comfortable.
不要
Don't.
你不能这么做
You can't run over here at the first sign of trouble.
我以为我失败了
I was losing it. I had to see you.
幸运的是罗宾自投罗网
Luckily taking Robin out works.
只是一个人而已
Grabs a handful.
想个办法把他也弄出来
Best to get him out of the way.
他总是很多疑
He was suspicious.
永远是
Always is.
他很聪明
Didn't say he was stupid.
损坏了相机镜头
He damaged the camera lens.
格林妮做的
Greenie was asking for it.
需要很多时间才能打败泰坦
It's taken a year to get the information I need to defeat theTitans.
别动
Could've ruined everything. Stay still.
- 杀了她  - 杀死女巫
- Kill her!  - Kill the witch!
杀死女巫 她是个恶魔
Kill the witch! She's a demon!
杀了她
Kill her now!
离开或死亡
Leave or die. Your choice.
马拉姆 泰拉
Terra Markov?
我听说你是一个特别的女孩
I heard you're a special girl.
这是真的吗
Is that true?
我的名字是斯莱德
My name is Slade.
看来我找到了
Looks like I got it.
不 你没有
Not yet, you haven't.
但你可以
But you could.
- 我们讨论过这个  - 我不是一个孩子
- We discussed this.  - I'm not a kid.
- 你说我们会在一起  - 还没到时候
- You said we'd be together.  - Not yet.
任务要紧
The contract is everything.
我们需要先处理眼前的事
We need total concentration for it.
你知道还有很多工作要做
You know it's taken a lot of work to get here.
- 尤其是你  - 我不想回去
- Especially by you.  - I don't wanna go back.
泰坦表现的好像他们在关心我
The Titans are always acting like they care so much.
这让我不知所措
It messes with my head.
马上就好 泰拉
Just a little longer, Terra.
有了血会的钱 我们将有自己的刺客联盟
With the money from blood we'll form our own league of assassins.
你和我
You and I.
将浪迹天涯
Together in every way.
我还没看到过这么多武器
I didn't see you bringing quite so many weapons to our new place.
- 如果你不喜欢  - 不不不 我喜欢
- If you don't like them...  - No, no. They're great.
有事吗
Is something up?
在训练场的事件之后
After the incident at the training field
我觉得你不需要我也可以统领他们
you met with members of the team without me.
是 这不一样
Yeah, we talked. But it wasn't a meeting.
柯莉 你知道我永远不会破坏你 对吧
Kori, you know I'd never undermine you, right?
他们需要你
They went to you.
你是…是一个伟大的领导者
You were... Are a great leader.
所以 他们盼着你回来了
So, they instinctively look to you, now that you're back.
毕竟 我不是你们这个世界的人
After all, I'm not even from your world.
不要这样
Hey. Stop.
泰坦们选择你来领导他们
You were chosen by the team to lead them.
而且我不能没有你
And have I told you how glad I am that you've chosen to move in with me?
我至少还有你
At least I was your first choice for that.
没错 你至少可以住我这
Yeah. Well, gar's got his house and Jaime couldn't afford the rent.
你这个家伙
You brat.
达米安 当然
Damian! Of course.
真会挑时间
Perfect timing.
- 什么事  - 他在做某事
- Solo?  - He's working on something.
待会再管
Have I mentioned he approves of us?
复议
So do I.
干嘛
Yeah? Problem?
没啥事
Not yet.
那就再见
Nice visit.
我知道我们之间有矛盾
I know I'm not easy to get close to.
我们要谈谈
We have that in common, I think.
而且我也有办法缓解你的精神问题
But I could teach you some meditation techniques.
让你更好的控制自己
It might help you stay in control.
那 那也许
Maybe. Maybe so.
还有 我们要举行聚餐活动
The other reason I'm here is to tell you the team's assembling in the common room.
你先走 我待会就来
I need a minute. You go on ahead.
他们知道了
They know about Robin.
他们不知道
They don't.
掠夺者 没问题吗
Raven, being nice?
我怎么不知道有聚餐这一回事
And there's nothing scheduled.
除非他们知道我和你在合作
They know I'm working with you.
如果他们知道 就不会让她一个人过来
If they knew, she wouldn't have come alone.
除非他们想让我放下戒备
Unless they wanted to get my guard down.
我不知道我能不能成功
I don't think I can take them all if they're ready.
冷静  他们没有怀疑你
Calm yourself. The fools trust you.
放轻松
Use that.
惊喜
Surprise!
该死
Shit.
你们吓到我了
You guys scared me.
[泰拉 周年纪念日快乐]
你们干什么
We can see that.
- 为了我吗  - 是的
- Are those for me?  - They sure are.
作为你的一周年泰坦纪念日
For your one year anniversary as a member of the Titans.
- 渡鸦想出来的主意  - 我…
- It was all Raven's idea.  - I...
从没有人为我这么做过这样的事情
No one has ever done anything like this for me.
谢谢
Thanks.
非常感谢
Thanks a lot.
抹干眼泪 开始嗨皮吧
Dry those tears and let's get this party started, mama!
电脑处理完了
The computer's done.
- 血会的文件  - 让我们看看
- The one with blood's files.  - Let's take a look.
文件重构和集成完成
File reconstruction and integration complete.
这个科学家曾经为蜂巢工作
That scientist used to work for H.I.V.E.
没有找到尸体
Body never recovered.
似乎他的个人实验室仍在为
Seems his personal lab is still being paid for
血会的子公司服务
by one of blood's holding companies.
泰坦们应该来看下
The Titans should look into this.
看来你要错过为
Beast Boy's sending you pictures of Terra’s party.
泰拉举办的聚会了
Shame you're missing it.
你就这么点本事吗
You should go. Playing with teenagers is about your speed.
小子 激将法对我无用
I'm not gonna let you bait me, kid.
哦 可惜
Oh, what the hell.
切
Big man.
你不让我离开这里
Why not get me out of here so I can defend myself properly?
- 是不是你在害怕  - 真的吗
- Unless, you're afraid.  - Really?
把你放了 然后再打一架
You're down to hoping I'm gonna act like the biggest stooge in a b-movie?
你不这么想吗
Your outfit said give it a shot.
你以为你是谁
Grandson of the demon's head, you are not.
你只是一个小屁孩
You're an entitled brat.
当我崛起时你还不知在哪
I Rose from nothing while you had everything handed to you.
你只是一个跳梁小丑
You cost me my rightful place.
和你背叛的家庭
And the family you betrayed.
他们选择了你
They turned on me by choosing you.
达米安 刺客联盟没了
You took my old family, Damian.
不过我会再创造一个新的
So I'll take your new one.
我先离开会
I should reply.
我们走的瞧
I am well and will see you soon.
你更像另一个迪克
You're more of a dick.
卧底 别打扰我
Undercover. Don't bother me.
我不会花很多时间
Shame I don't have more time to break you down.
只要一个月 我就会让你跪地求饶
Inside a month, I'd have you bringing me my pipe and calling me papa.
斯勒德 待会再说
Slade? Get your head out of your ass.
- 听到吗  - 如果我们找到科学家
- You seeing this?  - And if we do find the scientist,
我们要活捉他
we want him alive at all cost.
五分钟后行动
We leave in five minutes.
乖乖呆着
Be a good boy.
小心
Careful. Watch your spacing.
[处理完成]
有有没有主意
Any idea what that gizmo is?
没有
Nothing good.
待会再吵
He's deleting. I vote we stop that.
让我们两个
That makes two of us.
好吧 三个
Okay, three.
远离电脑 就完事大吉
Step away from the computer. You won't be hurt.
你先去 我随后到
Go after him. I'll cover you.
我们应该留在聚会上
We should have stayed at the party.
没什么好抱怨
Quit complaining.
那我就奉陪到底
Oh, you wanna play?
差劲
That's it? Lame.
你想先问他什么
What do you want to ask him first?
倒霉
Bad luck for him.
至少不是一无所获
At least it wasn't one of us.
话没错
Yes, bad luck.
就是不能和他细谈了
That we couldn't speak with him about these.
也许他是个粉丝
Maybe he was a fan?
他们竟然在研究我们
Is it really a surprise they would study us?
我们几个月前就再与他们作战
We've been defeating them for months.
这里面竟然有你
And you were after them even before that.
他们调查的如此深入
But this stuff is so in-depth.
在调查我们的基因构造
Things on genetic makeup.
渡鸦与野兽男孩的
Theories on Raven's power.
力量来源
Beast Boy's too.
还有蓝甲虫
And Beetle's suit.
但为什么
What's it for?
把罗宾召回来
We need to get Robin back here.
你知道他这人又多不守纪
You know how stubborn he can be.
他是我们的成员
He's a titan. He needs to be here.
都怪蜂巢打扰了我们的聚会
Nothing like laser-spewing H.I.V.E drones to take you out of a party mood.
我决定明天中饭在中心区吃
I'm beat and I'm making lunch at the center tomorrow.
真会泼冷水
In more exciting news,
我明天也受邀参加凯文·史密斯的播客聚会
I've been invited to be on Kevin Smith's podcast at Metrocon tomorrow.
等下 星火有事宣布
Hold up, Starfire's got something to say.
由于今天晚上的发现
With what we discovered tonight,
我们将要提高警惕
we all need to be extra vigilant
不要疏忽大意
and not take any chances.
不是吧 那可是凯文·史密斯
Are you kidding me? It's Kevin Smith.
我没有说禁止你们自由行动
I didn't say don't do what you have planned.
提高警惕 还有保持通讯畅通
But keep your eyes and comm lines open at all times.
我觉得兄弟血会要有所行动了
I have a feeling whatever blood is planning tonight is just a prelude.
抱歉你的聚会以这种方式结束
Sorry your party was interrupted.
这也没办法
That's the way it goes.
别又跟以前一样
Don't let all that talk back there shake you up.
你知道我是你这边的
You know I got your back.
其他的事
It's other stuff.
什么
Like what?
我洗耳恭听
I'm all ears.
你笑起来更好看
You've a pretty smile.
你知道我怎么变成孤儿的吗
Do you know how I became an orphan?
嗯 你的父母去世了
Uh, your parents died?
不是
No.
因为我的能力 他们吓坏了
After I got powers, they freaked.
他们是我为异人
Thought I was possessed or something.
对不起
I'm sorry.
不要这样
Don't be.
我不需要你的怜悯
I don't need your pity.
我只是想拉近我们的关系
It can be a bond, you know?
团队里的每个人都有一个不幸过去
Everyone on the team's had it rough.
是啊
Yeah.
一个公主 穿着闪闪发光的丁字裤从垃圾桶找食物
I can tell Princess sparkle thong knows all about eating from a dumpster.
柯莉被她妹妹夺了权
Kori is a refugee being stalked by her homicidal sister.
杰米有一个爱他的家庭
Jaime has a family that loves him.
由于那个甲虫 他不能和他的家人生活在一起
And, because of the bug, odds are he's never seeing them face-to-face again.
每个英雄都有苦处
I think pain is what makes a hero.
金无足赤 人无完人
It's like a pressure that either forms a diamond or grinds you into dust.
开心果 你呢
But what about you, chuckles?
你又没有什么苦处
Aside from an unhealthy online presence, you're normal.
是啊 你是绿色的
Yeah, you're green.
你不会去改变它的
You wouldn't change it if you could.
你喜欢引人注目
You like the attention.
除此在外
Besides
你一切正常
it looks okay on you.
你没杀我
You didn't kill me.
这一次
This time.
说明不了什么 笨蛋
Don't get used to it, jerk.
高兴 开心
Yes! Yeah!
我最牛 哈哈
Whoo-hew! Yeah, baby! Ha-ha!
我最强
Oh, yeah, baby!
我们走吧
Let's go!
开心
Nice play.
一切就绪
Almost bought it myself.
我们明天行动
We move tomorrow.
我有点累了 加油
I'm tired, gar.
是的 当然 好的
Yeah, sure, totally get it.
明天见还有后天
See you tomorrow. And the next day.
我会搞的
Yeah, I got them all in.
我知道我是蠢货但我搞的定
Hey, I know I'm a noob but I got this.
再见
See you when you get here, .
这里一定有很多人
The guest of honor with one million followers is...
是这没错吧
Uh, here?
有人吗
Hello?
凯文或者其他人
Kevin? Other guy?
今天下午我们应该再好好把文件再复查一遍
I think we should look over the files again, this afternoon.
确保我们没有遗落什么
Make sure we didn't miss anything.
遵命
Sure thing.
一切安排听从组织
And per your orders, I'll check on Jaime and gar.
你不必这样做 但谢谢
You don't have to do that, but thanks.
还有
By the way...
我想我搞不定这个
The warlords of Okaara didn't teach me much about cooking.
看来要定外卖了
I think you should pick something up on the way back.
回见
See you soon, babe.
怎么了
What's going on?
早应该开门了
Not sure. It should be open.
也许他忘了
We got a new guy.
杰米
Jaime?
泰坦蓝甲虫被抓走了
Titans, Blue Beetle has been taken.
在塔上集合
Gather at the tower.
这里是柯莉和迪克 我们不在家
This is Kori and dick. We're not home now.
请留言
So leave a message.
星火接电话 我要去接野兽小子
Starfire, pick up if you're there. I'm going to get Beast Boy.
在塔楼汇合
Get to the tower now.
不是吧
Oh, come on, gar.
柯莉 你在吗
Kori, you here?
柯莉
Kori.
丧钟已敲响
Bad day, Nightwing?
末日来临
It's about to get worse.
你对其他人做了什么
What have you done with Kori and the others?
别担心
Don't fret.
你马上就回和他们见面了
I'm here to take you to them.
混蛋 休想
Bring it, asshole.
就这么点
Akido needs work.
你就这么点水平
Your spacing's for shit.
你太嫩了
You're overrated, kid.
该死
Damn it.
够了
Enough.
该结束了
Screw this.
格雷森 你逃了又如何
You could have died by the Blade with honor, Grayson.
手下败将
Loser.
任务完成了吗
Is it done?
是 搞定了
Yeah, we're good.
他在骗你
He's lying to you.
所有的都是谎言
About everything.
他以此为生
He had you pegged from the start.
他为了达到目的
That's how he does it.
不惜手段
Mixing truth with lies.
你就继续扯吧
You're so freaking annoying.
你知道什么
You don't know anything about him.
他救了我的命
He saved me.
让我猜猜 他让你只
Let me guess, he kept you isolated.
依赖他
Dependent.
敌视所有人
Told you everyone was your enemy.
然后训练你
Trained you, ruthlessly.
向你许下承诺
And promised you exactly what you wanted.
我知道他所有的套路
Believe me, I know.
我一直很讨厌你
I've always hated you.
还有其他人
You and all the others.
泰坦对待你像家人
The Titans treated you like family.
而你却背叛了我们
And you threw it all away.
闭嘴
Stop...
你先离开一会
Can't I leave you for two minutes?
我明白你为什么要杀了他了
I can see why you want him dead.
怎么了
What's wrong?
再过几个小时 我们就离开这里
In a few hours, we're gone.
任务完成了
It's as good as done.
很高兴终于结束了
Just glad this is over.
你已经卧底了一年了
You've been in deep cover for a year.
对他们有感情是完全正常的
It's perfectly normal to have feelings for them.
以后就只有我们两个了
But after this we can be together.
这不正是你所希望的吗
Just like you wanted.
别让他影响你
Concentrate on that.
电脑 跟踪泰拉马尔可夫的手机
Computer, track Terra Markov's phone.
已发现 主体正在移动
Discovered, subject is moving.
我想也是
I'll bet she is.
兄弟姐妹 我一再强调
Brothers and sisters, I have spoken many times
所谓的神
about false gods.
只不过是
These so-called heroes with no allegiance to our cause,
那些所谓的超级英雄
are nothing but secular idols and must be ended.
世间 只有我才是真正的神
This is the true house of faith and I am the one true god.
血兄弟万岁 万岁
Hail brother blood. Hail, hail!
现在圣光
Today, I am claiming their powers for us all.
已降临到我们身上
For we are the seeds of the next generation.
我们蜂巢的身上
We are the hive of humanity.
再也不会有人来阻止
And nothing will stand in our way.
我降下圣光
Raise me this holy day.
我们将主宰世界
The day of blood.
兄弟血会万岁 万岁
Hail brother blood. Hail...
这个地方让我毛骨悚然
Place gives me the creeps.
我听到了
I hear you.
伙计们 渡鸦有点不对劲
Huh? Guys, Raven's not moving.
这里有东西抑制了我的能力
Something's keeping me from using my powers to morph.
是的 机器就是这么设计的
Yeah, the machine's doing that.
是我把你们放了进去
But, I'm the one who put you here.
丧钟
Deathstroke.
你对罗宾做了什么
What have you done to Robin?
他嘴巴太臭了
I beat the crap out of him for being mouthy.
你们也想试试吗
Come on, you've all had the urge.
一旦我出来 我会揍你一顿
Once I get out, I'm gonna break you into little bits.
有理想
It's good to have goals, ese.
在你们死后我会好好的享受会的
Me, I'm having waffles, after you're dead.
顺便 向你们介绍一下我的助手
By the way, can I introduce you to my assistant?
我想你们已经见过了
I think you've met.
队友们 你们好啊
Hey, team, how's things?
泰拉 他对你做了什么
Terra, what did he do to you?
没什么我已经问了很多次
Nothing. And I've asked a bunch of times.
泰拉是我安插在你们队伍里
Terra was a key part of my plan.
的间谍
A natural double agent.
这不可能是真的
That can't be true.
就像我说的
What can I tell you, Goldilocks.
有得必有失去
You win some, you lose some.
我们视你为队友
We took you in.
诚心诚意帮助你
Helped you.
那就谢谢了
Yeah, well, thanks.
你们就等死吧
Now you're gonna die.
我还真有点不忍心啊
Geez, not a lot of gray area there, huh.
泰拉
Terra...
这地方让我想起了我父母的教会
Place reminds me of my parents' church.
一堆疯子
Bunch of crazies.
不知天高地厚的蝼蚁
Insolent trash.
你管谁叫蝼蚁
Who you calling trash?
冷静
Keep it together.
对我们的客人礼貌点
Let's be civil to our guests.
契约还没有完成
Our business is not yet complete.
没有完成
Sure it is.
你想要泰坦 我把他们带来
You wanted the Titans, and here they are.
不是全部
Not all of them.
少了夜翼
Not Nightwing.
这破坏了机器的平衡
It ruins the machine's symmetry.
死亡是不可避免的
We agreed some deaths might be unavoidable.
你要明白
Things happen.
我知道
I accept that.
而我也告诉过你
But I told you even in death there is life to be drawn.
尸体同样有用
Where is the body? Unless you have a body, you're one short.
所以我们的合同还不完整
Therefore, our contract is not complete.
幸运的是 我们还有备胎
Happily there is still a path to the salvation of our deal.
不是吗
Don't you agree?
很好
Excellent.
动手
Mayhem.
泰拉
Terra!
我要索要更多的报酬
I should have charged more.
有了她的力量 你犹如虎添翼
With her powers, you're getting an upgrade.
阿门
Amen.
现在 我们的契约已经完成
Now, our business is complete.
斯莱德 救我
Slade, help me.
对不起 孩子 生意就是生意
Sorry, kid. But a contract is a contract.
你会付出代价
You'll pay for this.
哦 甜心我也舍不得你
Oh, it's a shame you have to go, sweet cheeks.
我们相爱彼此
We would have been fantastic lovers.
我们对彼此一见钟情
You know, since we're both newly single.
开始
Let it begin!
你认为你是神吗 血兄弟
You think yourself a holy man, blood?
你只是个小人
You're filth.
缄口 罪人
Take heart, sinner.
你们将名垂青史
You are about to become part of the greater good.
要我们教你怎么成名吗
We're gonna show you the greater good.
就是踢你的屁股
By kicking your ass.
丧钟 上帝不会饶恕你的
No god is going to save you, Deathstroke.
血兄弟
Word to the wise, blood,
你要对他们做什么 快点做
whatever you're gonna do to them, do it quickly.
感觉不舒服
Not feeling so good.
他们罪有应得
I consider their pain a retribution for their sins against me.
对
Right.
你高兴就好
Have a nice day.
先别急着走 等这个环节过了再说
Oh, don't leave now, brother. Everyone stays for this part.
什么环节 血兄弟
What part is that, brother?
当他们的力量助我成神时
When their powers are transferred and I ascend to god state.
血弟兄们 圣光即将降临
Hail me, brethren, for the moment of ascendency has arrived.
万岁 血兄弟 万岁 万岁
Hail, brother blood. Hail, hail.
万岁 万岁万岁
兄弟血会万岁 万岁
Hail, brother blood. Hail...
没错我的子民们  你们将见证我…
Yes, my children, this vessel shall now transform me...
成神之…
And you are witness.
血兄弟 万岁 万岁 万岁
Hail, brother blood. Hail, hail.
我感到
I feel it.
爽
Yes!
我即将成神
My godhood is nearly complete.
赞美他
Praise him.
血兄弟万岁
All hail brother blood.
万岁 万岁
Hail, hail.
爽…
Yes...
我知道你会来的
I knew you'd come.
嗨 老大爷 这是你的
Hey, papa, here's your pipe.
不要感谢我
Save some for me.
你们就不明白我是天命之子吗
Don't you know, I am the chosen?
你们不知道 我是神…
Don't you know, I am divine...
我会杀了你
I'm gonna kill you.
你在利用我 不是吗
I was being studied, like all the rest, wasn't I?
你从一开始就计划这个权利
You planned this right from the start.
冷静下来
Calm down.
我的爱 不是你想的这样
This is all a big misunderstanding, love.
泰拉 不
Terra, no.
哦哦 该死
Oh, shit.
你这个异教徒
You heathen brats.
你毁了我的圣殿
You've destroyed my holy temple.
你夺走了我的神力
You've robbed me of my destiny.
我要杀了你
You will die.
你不会伤害…
You cannot harm...
不 滚开
No, you stay away from me.
你们这些恶魔
You demon filth.
他们不是恶魔
They're not demons.
我才是
Let me show you one.
什么鬼
What the hell?
我准备了这么久
I planned so long.
我是神 你们不明白吗
I was destined, can't you see?
我恳求你
Please, I beseech you.
以血兄弟的名义
I am blood.
我…
I...
我是…
I am...
原谅我
Saved.
我不会让他们抓住你的 我的爱
I won't let them cage you, my love.
快走
Come on.
孩子 再见
So long, kid.
泰拉…
Terra...
对不起
I'm sorry.
不 泰拉…
No, Terra...
- 不要…  - 我们必须离开这里
- No...  - We have to go. The place is gonna collapse.
泰拉
Terra!
可以问你个问题吗 你怎么会成为一个泰坦呢
So, let me ask you this, man, how do you become a titan exactly?
我的意思是 有没有试镜什么的
I mean, is there an audition? Do you look at videos?
我能不能成为一个泰坦
'Cause I've been working out, you know, I want in.
凯文 对我泰坦们泰坦来说
Well, Kev, I guess the most important thing to being a titan,
家庭最重要
is to have a strong sense of family.
有时我们也会因为性格不合
Some of us don't have our own, so, we support the ones that do.
而伤害彼此
Of course, an outgoing personality does hurt but, you know,
但你有超能力诶
you gotta have a power.
是挺帅的
Something cool.
帅 伙计你可以变身为动物 这也太酷炫了
Something cool? Listen, you turn into animals, man, that's beyond cool.
谢谢
Thanks.
这个能力不是来耍酷的
But, it's not just about the cool super powers,
穿上制服我们不能为所欲为
snazzy uniforms and daring adventures.
它使我们变得
It's about us helping each other grow.
更好
Be better people.
我知道你不想谈论队伍里的人 但我还是忍不住
Listen, I know you're not supposed to talk about this, but I just gotta ask.
想问问那个女孩
There's a new girl, right?
她对我们来说意义非凡
All I can say is that she's a wonderful addition to the team.
- 继续说  - 星火会杀了我的
- Come on, gar...  - Starfire would kill me.
这事就你知我知
There's no way Starfire is listening to this, man, she's brushing her hair.
不要 没门
Forget it. My lips are sealed.
他变成了只海豹
Whoa, man, he just turned into a seal, folks, I swear.
但是 加尔 她代替了土石女的位置吗
But really, gar, is she gonna, like, replace Terra?
泰拉
Terra?
是的 你应该知道很多关于她的故事
Yeah, you know, there are lots of stories about her.
我知道
I know.
哦 太好了
Ooh, too soon?
是啊
Yeah.
我不是这个意思 如果你不想…
I mean, that's cool honestly, if you don't wanna...
但是 我想说…
But, I'd like to say something...
很多人幻想过一个完美的人生
There are a lot of people who've been handed a rough life.
他们没有什么需求 但…
They never asked for it, but...
他们尽其所能
They do what they can.
他们害怕被伤害
Many of them can't rise above the hurt.
但这太难了
It's just too hard.
但是最后 一切轰然倒塌时
But in the end, when the chips were down,
她找到了自我
and she finally showed her true self,
泰拉马科夫是我见过的
Terra Markov was like a diamond.
最伟大的人
Most beautiful thing that I'd ever seen.
后续彩蛋 请勿走开
就如我所说
I talk to the dead.
死亡不是终结
For no matter how rotted the corpse,
一切才刚刚开始
there's always a tiny wisp of life left.